GANNAVARAPU SAI ADITYA

Specialist Programmer

Infosys Ltd.

Pune, Maharashtra

Phone: +91 - 7032523251

Website: https://aditya-67.github.io GitHub: https://github.com/aditya-67/ML Email: adityagannavarapu.67@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Link

PROJECTS

Drawing with Machines, implementing Sketch RNN (Website)

Implemented using p5.js and sketch_rnn.js of Magenta, an open source research project exploring the role of machine learning as a tool in the creative process. Sketch RNN is trained on Quick Draw! doodle dataset of Google. It is generative model for vector drawings. If you start a drawing, it will finish it for you.

Gesture Pong, Gesture Controlled Pong game using Tensorflow.js and Object Detection API (Website)

Using TensorFlow Object detection API, created a game which can be controlled using the gestures of your hand from video in front of webcam. Wave your hand in front of webcam to control the paddle. Inspired from the implementation of Victor Dibia.

Speech Recognition (Wake-word Detection with a chime) (Video Demo)

This is a demo that I've developed to recognize audio commands and trained a model on a wake word to start taking audio input and converting it into text to derive intents using NLP.

Image Style Transfer using TensorFlow.js (Website)

This is an implementation of Neural Artistic Style Transfer running in browser using Tensorflow.js. This was inspired by the research paper <u>A Neural Algorithm of Artistic Style</u>. Converted the trained model to javascript using tensorflow.js and used it for running in a browser.

GAN Synth, Generating audio using GAN

Implementation of GAN Synth from Google Seedbank. Learned how to use GAN's to generate audio from given MIDI samples and use them to new samples. Future work is to learn about Audio style transfer for imparting certain style of audio to another audio.

Image Recognition, deployed to Heroku (Website)

Image Recognition - Dogs vs Cats, deployed to Heroku using Flask backend. A six layer CNN built using tflearn using the Kaggle Dataset. Upload an image of cat or dog, the model can predict the class.

Generating Music using LSTM

Using LSTM's in a Google Colab, we train a RNN with MIDI files of music to generate new music in MIDI format.

InShorts News Sentiment Analysis

Web-scrapping InShorts news using BeautifulSoup and Requests. Performing pre-processing of text data using NLP libraries (NLTK and SpaCy). Sentiment Analysis was performed using AFINN Lexicon and TextBlob.

3D visualization of Furniture using 3.js, deployed to Heroku (Website)

For more projects, please visit my personal website or GitHub profile.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE			
Sep, 2019 – Dec, 2019	ML Fellow, Fellowship.Al Incoming ML fellow at Fellowship.Al.		
July, 2018 – present	Specialist Programmer, Infosys I'm a full-stack developer working on Angular and .NET. With an active participation in the AI Track, an internal initiative of Infosys.		
2016 - 2017 2015 - 2016	Technical Secretary, MNIT SPORTS FESTIVAL, Annual Sports Fest. Consecutively held this position for two years. Designed and Developed the website of MST, responsive, mobile-friendly and dynamic.		
Aug - Nov,2016	Full-Stack Developer Intern, Third Dimension. Worked as a Full-Stack Developer in developing a e-commerce furniture website which uses Laravel, a PHP framework and POSTGRESQL in the back-end.		

EDUCATION			
2014-18	Graduation, Electrical Engineering Malaviya National Institute of Technology, Jaipur	(On a scale of 10) 5.08	
2012-14	Intermediate/+2 (Senior Secondary Education) Board of Intermediate Education Andhra Pradesh	95.4%	
2011-12	Matriculation (Central Board of Secondary Education)	(On a scale of 10) 9.8	

SKILL SET AND INTERESTS

- Programming Languages C, C++, Python, JavaScript, PHP.
- Front-End Web Development involving Angular, Ionic, HTML, CSS, jQuery, JS.
- Back-End Web Development involving .NET, PHP, MySQL, PHP Frameworks (LARAVEL),
- Machine Learning Regression, One-Shot Learning, Deep Learning, K-NN, SVM, Cluster Analysis, NLP, LSTM, GRU RNN, CNN
- Interests in Computer Vision, Reinforcement Learning, Genomics, GAN (General Adversarial Networks)

RELEVANT INFORMATION				
Courses	Completed Andrew NG's Machine Learning Course(Coursera) and Deep Learning Course (deeplearning.ai).			
Languages	English (working proficiency), Hindi (working proficiency), Telugu (Native).			

EXTRACURRICULLARS

- Technical Secretary, Electrical Engineering Society(EES), Student Body of Electrical Engineering Department, MNIT Jaipur.
- Web Head, MNIT SPORTS TOURNAMENT-2015, Annual Sports Fest.

PASTIME

- Playing Football
- Digital Art